<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:ror="http://rorweb.com/0.1/" >
<channel>
  <title>ROR Sitemap for http://www.edoxitraining.com/</title>
  <link>http://www.edoxitraining.com/</link>

<item>
     <link>http://www.edoxitraining.com/</link>
     <title>Accredited Professional Training Center in Dubai | Edoxi Training </title>
     <description>Leading educational training institute in Dubai offering extensive career-orientated courses including Computer, Accounting, Language and Management Courses for individuals and corporates by highly experienced trainers. Call us at 043801666  to join our courses.</description>
     <ror:updatePeriod>weekly</ror:updatePeriod>
     <ror:sortOrder>0</ror:sortOrder>
     <ror:resourceOf>sitemap</ror:resourceOf>
</item>
<item>
     <link>http://www.edoxitraining.com/about</link>
     <title>About Edoxi - Edoxi Training Center - Dubai, UAE</title>
     <description>The most excellent educational training center in Dubai offers career-orientated courses to the aspirant professionals. Each of our courses is specifically designed by industry experts to provide individuals with the necessary skills they can straight away be applied at your workplace.</description>
     <ror:updatePeriod>weekly</ror:updatePeriod>
     <ror:sortOrder>1</ror:sortOrder>
     <ror:resourceOf>sitemap</ror:resourceOf>
</item>
<item>
     <link>http://www.edoxitraining.com/category/digital-marketing-courses-in-dubai</link>
     <title>Digital Marketing Training Courses Dubai | Digital Marketing Institute</title>
     <description>Get global standard digital marketing &amp; social selling education form Edoxi Training Institute Dubai! Learn advanced techniques and mythologies of SEO, SEM, SMO, Content, ORM, Analytics, and Email Marketing in one course. Call us for booking!  </description>
     <ror:updatePeriod>weekly</ror:updatePeriod>
     <ror:sortOrder>1</ror:sortOrder>
     <ror:resourceOf>sitemap</ror:resourceOf>
</item>
<item>
     <link>http://www.edoxitraining.com/digital-marketing-specialist-training-course-in-dubai</link>
     <title>Digital Marketing Courses in Dubai - Professional Digital Marketing Certification  </title>
     <description>Become a successful digital marketing specialist in Dubai &amp; get wide range of opportunities in various companies to start your career in digital marketing. Know the importance of digital marketing strategies in our classes &amp; grow your business guaranteed.</description>
     <ror:updatePeriod>weekly</ror:updatePeriod>
     <ror:sortOrder>1</ror:sortOrder>
     <ror:resourceOf>sitemap</ror:resourceOf>
</item>
<item>
     <link>http://www.edoxitraining.com/google-analytics-training-course-in-dubai</link>
     <title>Google Analytics Training Classes in Dubai | Edoxi Training Institute  </title>
     <description>Edoxi training institute provides incredible Google Analytics Training in Dubai for students or professionals to learn latest trends of Google Analytics tool with the help of conceptual theory, case studies and highly experienced digital marketing experts</description>
     <ror:updatePeriod>weekly</ror:updatePeriod>
     <ror:sortOrder>1</ror:sortOrder>
     <ror:resourceOf>sitemap</ror:resourceOf>
</item>
<item>
     <link>http://www.edoxitraining.com/seo-specialist-training-course-in-dubai</link>
     <title>SEO Courses - Advance SEO Specialist Training in Dubai   </title>
     <description>Learn advance and latest techniques of search engine optimization (SEO) at Edoxi Training Institute! Our SEO Training courses will provide you enough insights to learns, understand and implement SEO strategy to improve SERP Ranking and website visitors tr</description>
     <ror:updatePeriod>weekly</ror:updatePeriod>
     <ror:sortOrder>1</ror:sortOrder>
     <ror:resourceOf>sitemap</ror:resourceOf>
</item>
<item>
     <link>http://www.edoxitraining.com/social-media-specialist-training-course-in-dubai</link>
     <title>Social Media Marketing - Certified SMO Training Courses in Dubai   </title>
     <description>Get advance training to become social media expert in Dubai! Our specialized social media marketing courses help you to execute social campaigns successfully and easily increase the business exposure, brand awareness, boost traffic &amp; sales to your busines</description>
     <ror:updatePeriod>weekly</ror:updatePeriod>
     <ror:sortOrder>1</ror:sortOrder>
     <ror:resourceOf>sitemap</ror:resourceOf>
</item>
<item>
     <link>http://www.edoxitraining.com/category/administration-and-secretarial-courses-in-dubai</link>
     <title>Administration Courses - Secretarial &amp; Document Controller Training in Dubai</title>
     <description>Get advantage of administration training courses in your professional Career! Join our training courses like secretarial and document control courses help you to bring your career to next level and successful life. </description>
     <ror:updatePeriod>weekly</ror:updatePeriod>
     <ror:sortOrder>1</ror:sortOrder>
     <ror:resourceOf>sitemap</ror:resourceOf>
</item>
<item>
     <link>http://www.edoxitraining.com/document-controller-training-course-in-dubai</link>
     <title>Document Controller Courses in Dubai | Edoxi Training Institute  </title>
     <description>Join our document controller courses and develop your skills to become professional document controller! Our excellent course designed by experts who have plenty of knowledge in their respective fields. Schedule a demo class! </description>
     <ror:updatePeriod>weekly</ror:updatePeriod>
     <ror:sortOrder>1</ror:sortOrder>
     <ror:resourceOf>sitemap</ror:resourceOf>
</item>
<item>
     <link>http://www.edoxitraining.com/office-management-training-course-in-dubai</link>
     <title>Office Management Courses in Dubai | Edoxi Training Institute  </title>
     <description>Specifically designed office management courses for office administrators, admin staff, secretaries and personal assistants to enhance their professional skills and do the tasks effectively. Join our courses to improve your performance and develop yoursel</description>
     <ror:updatePeriod>weekly</ror:updatePeriod>
     <ror:sortOrder>1</ror:sortOrder>
     <ror:resourceOf>sitemap</ror:resourceOf>
</item>
<item>
     <link>http://www.edoxitraining.com/secretarial-training-course-in-dubai</link>
     <title>Secretarial Skills Training Courses in Dubai | Edoxi Training Institute  </title>
     <description>Professional Training Institutes provides quality secretarial training courses for interested candidates in Dubai! Our course will help you regularly update yourself with the latest trends and practices that will help you to run business smoothly and plan</description>
     <ror:updatePeriod>weekly</ror:updatePeriod>
     <ror:sortOrder>1</ror:sortOrder>
     <ror:resourceOf>sitemap</ror:resourceOf>
</item>
<item>
     <link>http://www.edoxitraining.com/speed-typing-training-course-in-dubai</link>
     <title>Speed Typing Training Courses in Dubai | Edoxi Training Institute  </title>
     <description>Improve your typing speed to become more productive at your work place! Edoxi training institute offers speed typing training courses for interested candidates in Dubai. Call us for more details.</description>
     <ror:updatePeriod>weekly</ror:updatePeriod>
     <ror:sortOrder>1</ror:sortOrder>
     <ror:resourceOf>sitemap</ror:resourceOf>
</item>
<item>
     <link>http://www.edoxitraining.com/category/erp-courses-in-dubai</link>
     <title>ERP Technical Courses - Fully Functional ERP Training Classes in Dubai </title>
     <description>Professional ERP training institute offers the finest range of SAP ERP functional courses for interested Individuals! Join ERP training classes for a bright and successful career in this field. Call us now!</description>
     <ror:updatePeriod>weekly</ror:updatePeriod>
     <ror:sortOrder>1</ror:sortOrder>
     <ror:resourceOf>sitemap</ror:resourceOf>
</item>
<item>
     <link>http://www.edoxitraining.com/oracle-apps-dba-training-course-in-dubai</link>
     <title>Oracle Apps DBA Training Institute in Dubai, UAE - Edoxi Training Institute  </title>
     <description>Leading Oracle Apps DBA training institute in Dubai with 100% placement guarantee. Career oriented Oracle Apps DBA training by industry professionals who will make sure that you understand the advanced ideas &amp; concepts of this course to become a master in</description>
     <ror:updatePeriod>weekly</ror:updatePeriod>
     <ror:sortOrder>1</ror:sortOrder>
     <ror:resourceOf>sitemap</ror:resourceOf>
</item>
<item>
     <link>http://www.edoxitraining.com/oracle-financials-training-course-in-dubai</link>
     <title>Oracle Courses - Financial Oracle Training in Dubai  </title>
     <description>Dubai’s leading Institute of professional education providing oracle courses for professional to learn advance way to use financial oracle applications for various operations in performance management, finance, governance, etc. Call us and join course tod</description>
     <ror:updatePeriod>weekly</ror:updatePeriod>
     <ror:sortOrder>1</ror:sortOrder>
     <ror:resourceOf>sitemap</ror:resourceOf>
</item>
<item>
     <link>http://www.edoxitraining.com/oracle-hrms-training-course-in-dubai</link>
     <title>Oracle HRMS Courses - Certified Oracle Training in Dubai  </title>
     <description>Oracle HRMS perfect for creating a standard platform for any Organizations!  Join our Oracle HRMS Training courses to learn manage HR information brilliantly, ordered, represented, make easy business management and classify your own reports. Call us today</description>
     <ror:updatePeriod>weekly</ror:updatePeriod>
     <ror:sortOrder>1</ror:sortOrder>
     <ror:resourceOf>sitemap</ror:resourceOf>
</item>
<item>
     <link>http://www.edoxitraining.com/oracle-purchase-training-course-in-dubai</link>
     <title>Oracle Purchase Training Centre in Dubai - Edoxi Training Institute  </title>
     <description>We are offering finest Oracle Purchase training in Dubai at affordable rates for interested candidates. Our programme will help to learn how to pertain document security, approving procedures, how to mechanize the process of order creation, how to manage </description>
     <ror:updatePeriod>weekly</ror:updatePeriod>
     <ror:sortOrder>1</ror:sortOrder>
     <ror:resourceOf>sitemap</ror:resourceOf>
</item>
<item>
     <link>http://www.edoxitraining.com/sap-abap-training-course-in-dubai</link>
     <title>SAP ABAP Training Courses in Dubai | Edoxi Training Institute  </title>
     <description>Get your SAP ABAP certification from renowned Edoxi Training Institute! We provide SAP ABAP classes in Dubai at present for beginners by highly experienced SAP training instructors! Join our SAP ABAP training course now! </description>
     <ror:updatePeriod>weekly</ror:updatePeriod>
     <ror:sortOrder>1</ror:sortOrder>
     <ror:resourceOf>sitemap</ror:resourceOf>
</item>
<item>
     <link>http://www.edoxitraining.com/sap-basis-training-course-in-dubai</link>
     <title>SAP Training Courses in Dubai - Basic SAP Training for Beginners  </title>
     <description>Learn diverse characteristics of SAP Application at Edoxi Training Institute! Our SAP Training courses help you to set-up various SAP products to improve existing systems, archiving of information, captivating backups, gap management all very important ta</description>
     <ror:updatePeriod>weekly</ror:updatePeriod>
     <ror:sortOrder>1</ror:sortOrder>
     <ror:resourceOf>sitemap</ror:resourceOf>
</item>
<item>
     <link>http://www.edoxitraining.com/sap-business-one-training-course-in-dubai</link>
     <title>SAP -Business -One-Training  </title>
     <description>SAP -Business -One-Training  </description>
     <ror:updatePeriod>weekly</ror:updatePeriod>
     <ror:sortOrder>1</ror:sortOrder>
     <ror:resourceOf>sitemap</ror:resourceOf>
</item>
<item>
     <link>http://www.edoxitraining.com/sap-fico-training-course-in-dubai</link>
     <title>SAP FICO Training Courses in Dubai | Edoxi Training Institute  </title>
     <description>SAP Authorized training centre in Dubai “Edoxi Training Institute”! SAP FICO is a cost controlling and finance module in SAP. Our course is specially designed for beginners which allow examining financial situation of a company and assisting better financ</description>
     <ror:updatePeriod>weekly</ror:updatePeriod>
     <ror:sortOrder>1</ror:sortOrder>
     <ror:resourceOf>sitemap</ror:resourceOf>
</item>
<item>
     <link>http://www.edoxitraining.com/sap-hr-training-course-in-dubai</link>
     <title>SAP HR Training - SAP HR Certification Courses in Dubai   </title>
     <description>Get the best SAP HR Training in Dubai by our experts to lead your dream with many career opportunities. Our course is highly structured and gives quality training to our students which help them to accomplish SAP HR certification with ease.</description>
     <ror:updatePeriod>weekly</ror:updatePeriod>
     <ror:sortOrder>1</ror:sortOrder>
     <ror:resourceOf>sitemap</ror:resourceOf>
</item>
<item>
     <link>http://www.edoxitraining.com/sap-mm-training-course-in-dubai</link>
     <title>SAP MM Training Courses in Dubai | Edoxi Training Institute  </title>
     <description>Enrol for recognised SAP MM training institute to get full knowledge of SAP MM module including many elements and sub-elements which comprise of Master Data, Inventory, and Purchasing. Join our training sessions now!</description>
     <ror:updatePeriod>weekly</ror:updatePeriod>
     <ror:sortOrder>1</ror:sortOrder>
     <ror:resourceOf>sitemap</ror:resourceOf>
</item>
<item>
     <link>http://www.edoxitraining.com/sap-netweaver-training-course-in-dubai</link>
     <title>SAP NetWeaver Training Courses Dubai | Edoxi Training Institute  </title>
     <description>Top rated institute for SAP NetWeaver course in Dubai! Our SAP NetWeaver training offers progress &amp; runtime environment for SAP apps and can be utilized for custom development and integrating with many systems and applications. We arrange individuals &amp; co</description>
     <ror:updatePeriod>weekly</ror:updatePeriod>
     <ror:sortOrder>1</ror:sortOrder>
     <ror:resourceOf>sitemap</ror:resourceOf>
</item>
<item>
     <link>http://www.edoxitraining.com/sap-pm-training-course-in-dubai</link>
     <title>SAP PM Training Courses in Dubai | Edoxi Training Institute  </title>
     <description>SAP plant maintenance training - Join SAP PM Courses to learn and understand company structure setup necessary for PM, diverse business process &amp; SAP transactions. Our centre is equipped with incredible facilities and infrastructure which help students to</description>
     <ror:updatePeriod>weekly</ror:updatePeriod>
     <ror:sortOrder>1</ror:sortOrder>
     <ror:resourceOf>sitemap</ror:resourceOf>
</item>
<item>
     <link>http://www.edoxitraining.com/sap-pp-training-course-in-dubai</link>
     <title>SAP PP Training Courses in Dubai - SAP Production Planning (PP) Institute  </title>
     <description>Edoxi Training Institute delivers placement focused SAP PP Training to help managers in &amp; beginners who desire to build a career in the production area. Our course will determine few important elements of SAP PP such as Work center, CRP, BOM, Data Center,</description>
     <ror:updatePeriod>weekly</ror:updatePeriod>
     <ror:sortOrder>1</ror:sortOrder>
     <ror:resourceOf>sitemap</ror:resourceOf>
</item>
<item>
     <link>http://www.edoxitraining.com/sap-sd-training-course-in-dubai</link>
     <title>SAP SD (Sales and Distribution) Courses in Dubai | Edoxi Training Institute  </title>
     <description>SAP SD module is closely incorporated in all business process to manage selling, billing or shipping of the products! Join our SAP SD training courses to understand real world scenarios of the customers and gain real-time skills and practical experience t</description>
     <ror:updatePeriod>weekly</ror:updatePeriod>
     <ror:sortOrder>1</ror:sortOrder>
     <ror:resourceOf>sitemap</ror:resourceOf>
</item>
<item>
     <link>http://www.edoxitraining.com/sap-wm-training-course-in-dubai</link>
     <title>SAP WM Training in Dubai, Classes, Courses | Edoxi Training Institute  </title>
     <description>Get placement oriented SAP WM Training at Edoxi Training Institute! Best SAP WM Training course institute in Dubai at presently. Fast track training available for candidates who want to complete the course very quickly! Don’t miss this opportunity.</description>
     <ror:updatePeriod>weekly</ror:updatePeriod>
     <ror:sortOrder>1</ror:sortOrder>
     <ror:resourceOf>sitemap</ror:resourceOf>
</item>
<item>
     <link>http://www.edoxitraining.com/category/designing-courses-in-dubai</link>
     <title>Designing Courses - Graphic, Adobe, Web Design Courses in Dubai</title>
     <description>Professional Designing Courses help you to learn the advanced technique of designing courses such as Adobe, CorelDraw, graphic designing, Adobe Photoshop, video editing and website designing. Join courses and get professionals benefits. </description>
     <ror:updatePeriod>weekly</ror:updatePeriod>
     <ror:sortOrder>1</ror:sortOrder>
     <ror:resourceOf>sitemap</ror:resourceOf>
</item>
<item>
     <link>http://www.edoxitraining.com/adobe-flash-training-course-in-dubai</link>
     <title>Adobe Flash Training Classes &amp; Certification in Dubai - Edoxi Training Institute  </title>
     <description>One of the best Adobe Flash training institutes in Dubai for interested candidates to get your dream job. We teach our students the use of animation techniques to create Flash projects easily. Our Adobe Flash certification is provided by certified experts</description>
     <ror:updatePeriod>weekly</ror:updatePeriod>
     <ror:sortOrder>1</ror:sortOrder>
     <ror:resourceOf>sitemap</ror:resourceOf>
</item>
<item>
     <link>http://www.edoxitraining.com/adobe-premier-pro-training-course-in-dubai</link>
     <title>Premiere Pro Classes - Adobe Premiere Pro Training in Dubai  </title>
     <description>Enroll Adobe Premiere Pro training to make high-quality amazing videos. We give training and complete knowledge on the tools and tactics available in this software to import videos, do editing, append effects and transitions, and then export the video pro</description>
     <ror:updatePeriod>weekly</ror:updatePeriod>
     <ror:sortOrder>1</ror:sortOrder>
     <ror:resourceOf>sitemap</ror:resourceOf>
</item>
<item>
     <link>http://www.edoxitraining.com/adobe-after-effects-training-course-in-dubai</link>
     <title>Adobe After Effects Training Classes in Dubai - Edoxi Training Institute  </title>
     <description>Get finest Adobe After Effects training in Dubai to learn building videos, doing animation and special effects at Edoxi Training Institute. Take your graphic designer skills to the next level with us! Get to us to be a master of Adobe After Effects softwa</description>
     <ror:updatePeriod>weekly</ror:updatePeriod>
     <ror:sortOrder>1</ror:sortOrder>
     <ror:resourceOf>sitemap</ror:resourceOf>
</item>
<item>
     <link>http://www.edoxitraining.com/coreldraw-training-course-in-dubai</link>
     <title>CorelDraw Training Centre in Dubai - Edoxi Training Institute  </title>
     <description>Get professional CorelDraw training in Dubai to build and edit any graphics image, amazing logos, photo editing, image filtering, special effects and much more are possible with our training programme. For inquiry call us at +971 43801666!</description>
     <ror:updatePeriod>weekly</ror:updatePeriod>
     <ror:sortOrder>1</ror:sortOrder>
     <ror:resourceOf>sitemap</ror:resourceOf>
</item>
<item>
     <link>http://www.edoxitraining.com/graphic-designing-training-course-in-dubai</link>
     <title>Graphic Design Courses in Dubai | Edoxi Training Institute  </title>
     <description>Join advance graphic Designing Courses at Edoxi Training Institute to become master of all aspects of graphic designing such as brochures, logo, poster, newspaper, marketing collaterals, newsletters, magazine design and interactive materials. Call us for </description>
     <ror:updatePeriod>weekly</ror:updatePeriod>
     <ror:sortOrder>1</ror:sortOrder>
     <ror:resourceOf>sitemap</ror:resourceOf>
</item>
<item>
     <link>http://www.edoxitraining.com/adobe-illustrator-training-course-in-dubai</link>
     <title>Adobe Illustrator Training Courses in Dubai | Edoxi Training Institute  </title>
     <description>Industry standard vector graphics drawing software Adobe Illustrator training open for everyone at Edoxi training institute!  Join advance training session of adobe illustrator courses to become master in this filed and career growth. Call us! </description>
     <ror:updatePeriod>weekly</ror:updatePeriod>
     <ror:sortOrder>1</ror:sortOrder>
     <ror:resourceOf>sitemap</ror:resourceOf>
</item>
<item>
     <link>http://www.edoxitraining.com/adobe-indesign-training-course-in-dubai</link>
     <title>Adobe Indesign Training in Dubai | Edoxi Training Institute  </title>
     <description>Adobe InDesign is most widely used software for Graphic Design work! We provide Adobe InDesign software training for professionals who work with layered documents, magazines, and newspapers. Get InDesign training and create masterpiece of your creativity </description>
     <ror:updatePeriod>weekly</ror:updatePeriod>
     <ror:sortOrder>1</ror:sortOrder>
     <ror:resourceOf>sitemap</ror:resourceOf>
</item>
<item>
     <link>http://www.edoxitraining.com/adobe-photoshop-training-course-in-dubai</link>
     <title>Adobe Photoshop Courses in Dubai | Edoxi Training Institute  </title>
     <description>Join our Adobe authorised training Center in Dubai to learn many amazing things of Photoshop Software!  Our skilful and experienced faculty team teach all extensive aspects of Photoshop to gain in-depth knowledge and application techniques to make your de</description>
     <ror:updatePeriod>weekly</ror:updatePeriod>
     <ror:sortOrder>1</ror:sortOrder>
     <ror:resourceOf>sitemap</ror:resourceOf>
</item>
<item>
     <link>http://www.edoxitraining.com/video-editing-training-course-in-dubai</link>
     <title>Video Editing Courses for Industry Professionals in Dubai | Edoxi Training Institute  </title>
     <description>We offer video editing training courses to empower students and individuals to attain the high skills of audio &amp; video editing. Well qualified professionals will make you master of video editing by improving your skills in short time. </description>
     <ror:updatePeriod>weekly</ror:updatePeriod>
     <ror:sortOrder>1</ror:sortOrder>
     <ror:resourceOf>sitemap</ror:resourceOf>
</item>
<item>
     <link>http://www.edoxitraining.com/web-designing-training-course-in-dubai</link>
     <title>Web Designing Training Courses in Dubai | Edoxi Training Institute  </title>
     <description>Professional Training Center offers web designing training courses for students and individuals who are interested to learn advance responsive web designing to create user-friendly and creative websites. Get quality training which helps you learn key aspe</description>
     <ror:updatePeriod>weekly</ror:updatePeriod>
     <ror:sortOrder>1</ror:sortOrder>
     <ror:resourceOf>sitemap</ror:resourceOf>
</item>
<item>
     <link>http://www.edoxitraining.com/category/engineering-and-cad-courses-in-dubai</link>
     <title>AutoCAD Courses in Dubai - Engineering &amp; CAD Training Courses</title>
     <description>Cad courses in Dubai - Join professionals Engineering and AutoCAD Courses at Edoxi training institute Dubai! Our Experienced and Skilled Instructors help you to learn CAD commands to plan, develop, document and represent a complete AutoCAD Projects easily</description>
     <ror:updatePeriod>weekly</ror:updatePeriod>
     <ror:sortOrder>1</ror:sortOrder>
     <ror:resourceOf>sitemap</ror:resourceOf>
</item>
<item>
     <link>http://www.edoxitraining.com/autocad-2d-training-course-in-dubai</link>
     <title>AutoCAD 2D Training Certification in Dubai - Edoxi Training Institute  </title>
     <description>Certified AutoCAD 2D training courses available at affordable rates! AutoCAD is most extensively used drafting software around the world by architectural &amp; engineering organizations. Grab opportunity and become a successful person by learning AutoCAD 2D c</description>
     <ror:updatePeriod>weekly</ror:updatePeriod>
     <ror:sortOrder>1</ror:sortOrder>
     <ror:resourceOf>sitemap</ror:resourceOf>
</item>
<item>
     <link>http://www.edoxitraining.com/3ds-max-training-course-in-dubai</link>
     <title>3ds Max Training in Dubai | Edoxi Training Institute  </title>
     <description>3ds Max software well known for modelling and rendering tools! Join our advance 3ds max training at Edoxi institute and learn 3ds Max interface to build 3D professional animations and models as per your needs.  Call us 971581236600 for more details!</description>
     <ror:updatePeriod>weekly</ror:updatePeriod>
     <ror:sortOrder>1</ror:sortOrder>
     <ror:resourceOf>sitemap</ror:resourceOf>
</item>
<item>
     <link>http://www.edoxitraining.com/autocad-3d-training-course-in-dubai</link>
     <title>3D AutoCAD Training - 3D CAD Courses in Dubai - Edoxi Training Institute  </title>
     <description>Edoxi training institute is offering finest coaching of 3D AutoCAD design and engineering software for students and also professionals. Our course includes inventor training, NavisWorks training, Design and Visualisation training and more. Get trained by </description>
     <ror:updatePeriod>weekly</ror:updatePeriod>
     <ror:sortOrder>1</ror:sortOrder>
     <ror:resourceOf>sitemap</ror:resourceOf>
</item>
<item>
     <link>http://www.edoxitraining.com/autocad-electrical-training-course-in-dubai</link>
     <title>AutoCAD Electrical Courses in Dubai | Edoxi Training Institute  </title>
     <description>Right coaching is necessary to utilize AutoCAD Electrical swiftly and successfully! Edoxi training institute offers AutoCAD Electrical Courses for students to learn advanced techniques to build electrical control design, schematic design, managing project</description>
     <ror:updatePeriod>weekly</ror:updatePeriod>
     <ror:sortOrder>1</ror:sortOrder>
     <ror:resourceOf>sitemap</ror:resourceOf>
</item>
<item>
     <link>http://www.edoxitraining.com/autocad-mep-training-course-in-dubai</link>
     <title>MEP Courses in Dubai - AutoCAD MEP Training Institute  </title>
     <description>We offer AutoCAD MEP training courses with best in industry tactics. Our trainer assists individuals to give training to plumbing engineers, mechanical, drafters and other concerned departments in Dubai, UAE. Enroll now!</description>
     <ror:updatePeriod>weekly</ror:updatePeriod>
     <ror:sortOrder>1</ror:sortOrder>
     <ror:resourceOf>sitemap</ror:resourceOf>
</item>
<item>
     <link>http://www.edoxitraining.com/bim-training-course-in-dubai</link>
     <title>BIM Training Courses in Dubai | Edoxi Training Institute  </title>
     <description>Professional Training Institute offers BIM Training Courses for who are interested!  Learn advanced techniques to find the clear insight of design, construction, BIM Drivers and easily collaborative building information for modelling (BIM) projects.</description>
     <ror:updatePeriod>weekly</ror:updatePeriod>
     <ror:sortOrder>1</ror:sortOrder>
     <ror:resourceOf>sitemap</ror:resourceOf>
</item>
<item>
     <link>http://www.edoxitraining.com/revit-architecture-training-course-in-dubai</link>
     <title>Revit Architecture Training Courses in Dubai | Edoxi Training Institute   </title>
     <description>New Engineering Autodesk Revit Architecture brings together architects and developers! Enroll advance Revit Architecture Training course to enhance your career &amp; take it to the next level in construction Industry. All sessions are provided by industry pro</description>
     <ror:updatePeriod>weekly</ror:updatePeriod>
     <ror:sortOrder>1</ror:sortOrder>
     <ror:resourceOf>sitemap</ror:resourceOf>
</item>
<item>
     <link>http://www.edoxitraining.com/revit-structure-training-course-in-dubai</link>
     <title>Autodesk Revit Structure Courses in Dubai | Edoxi Training Institute  </title>
     <description>Get advance Autodesk Revit Structure Training from Edoxi Training Institute!  Our training courses help individuals to become an expert in revit structure to understand the new features of structural projects easily.</description>
     <ror:updatePeriod>weekly</ror:updatePeriod>
     <ror:sortOrder>1</ror:sortOrder>
     <ror:resourceOf>sitemap</ror:resourceOf>
</item>
<item>
     <link>http://www.edoxitraining.com/revit-mep-training-course-in-dubai</link>
     <title>Revit MEP Training in Dubai | Edoxi Training Institute  </title>
     <description>Exclusively designed Autodesk Revit MEP Training Courses for students to learn &amp; implement the ideas of BIM and prompt the tools for parametric engineering design along with documentation using Revit MEP Software.</description>
     <ror:updatePeriod>weekly</ror:updatePeriod>
     <ror:sortOrder>1</ror:sortOrder>
     <ror:resourceOf>sitemap</ror:resourceOf>
</item>
<item>
     <link>http://www.edoxitraining.com/microstation-training-course-in-dubai</link>
     <title>Microstation Training Centre in Dubai, UAE | Edoxi Training Institute  </title>
     <description>Renowned Microstation Training Institute provides MicroStation training for engineers to meet their challenging needs related to engineering, AECO, geospatial professionals, construction and architectural fields. Call us at 971581236600 to enrol now! </description>
     <ror:updatePeriod>weekly</ror:updatePeriod>
     <ror:sortOrder>1</ror:sortOrder>
     <ror:resourceOf>sitemap</ror:resourceOf>
</item>
<item>
     <link>http://www.edoxitraining.com/staad-pro-training-course-in-dubai</link>
     <title>STAAD pro Training Courses in Dubai | Edoxi Training Institute  </title>
     <description>Edoxi Training Institute offers structural analysis and design (STAAD ) pro software training courses by professional trainers to mechanize the work by eliminating tedious &amp; lengthy processes of manual methods.</description>
     <ror:updatePeriod>weekly</ror:updatePeriod>
     <ror:sortOrder>1</ror:sortOrder>
     <ror:resourceOf>sitemap</ror:resourceOf>
</item>
<item>
     <link>http://www.edoxitraining.com/vray-training-course-in-dubai</link>
     <title>VRay Course Training Institute in Dubai - Edoxi Training Institute  </title>
     <description>Leading VRay Centers in Dubai, offering VRay training courses to make you perfect with VRay and its use. VRay is a computer-generated imagery rendering software application which includes individual materials and lighting system. Attend our classes and ma</description>
     <ror:updatePeriod>weekly</ror:updatePeriod>
     <ror:sortOrder>1</ror:sortOrder>
     <ror:resourceOf>sitemap</ror:resourceOf>
</item>
<item>
     <link>http://www.edoxitraining.com/interior-design-training-course-in-dubai</link>
     <title>Interior Design Courses in Dubai | Edoxi Training Institute  </title>
     <description>Turn your creativity and concepts into quality designs by interior design training course in Dubai! Our ideologies and methodologies help you to become master for interior designing and create a beautiful design for hotels, public places, home, museums, o</description>
     <ror:updatePeriod>weekly</ror:updatePeriod>
     <ror:sortOrder>1</ror:sortOrder>
     <ror:resourceOf>sitemap</ror:resourceOf>
</item>
<item>
     <link>http://www.edoxitraining.com/etabs-training-course-in-dubai</link>
     <title>ETABS Software Training &amp; Classes in Dubai | Edoxi Training Institute  </title>
     <description>Enroll for premium ETABS Training in Dubai for those who are highly interested. ETABS stands for Extended 3D Analysis of Building Systems. ETABS Software utilized by designers &amp; engineers transversely in a variety of industries, comprising of aerospace, a</description>
     <ror:updatePeriod>weekly</ror:updatePeriod>
     <ror:sortOrder>1</ror:sortOrder>
     <ror:resourceOf>sitemap</ror:resourceOf>
</item>
<item>
     <link>http://www.edoxitraining.com/category/project-management-courses-in-dubai</link>
     <title>Project Management Courses - PMP Training Program in Dubai</title>
     <description>PMP Training Program specially designed for improving the professional’s skills for their career growth! Join our effective project management courses for strategic planning, manage, execute, and control projects easily in any industry. Call us to select </description>
     <ror:updatePeriod>weekly</ror:updatePeriod>
     <ror:sortOrder>1</ror:sortOrder>
     <ror:resourceOf>sitemap</ror:resourceOf>
</item>
<item>
     <link>http://www.edoxitraining.com/microsoft-project-msp-training-course-in-dubai</link>
     <title>MS Project Training - MSP Training Courses in Dubai  </title>
     <description>MS Project Training (MSP) Courses helpful to promote yourself to higher positions! Our MSP training program is designed to assist project managers to develop projects, assign resources to tasks, to track progress, managing budget, analyzing workloads that</description>
     <ror:updatePeriod>weekly</ror:updatePeriod>
     <ror:sortOrder>1</ror:sortOrder>
     <ror:resourceOf>sitemap</ror:resourceOf>
</item>
<item>
     <link>http://www.edoxitraining.com/pmp-training-course-in-dubai</link>
     <title>PMP Certification Training Courses in Dubai | Edoxi Training Institute    </title>
     <description>PMP Training - Promote your career to next level with PMP certification Courses at Edoxi Training Institute Dubai! Our PMP Certification courses assist professionals to enhance their real-world skills, manage projects and develop leadership skills. Join c</description>
     <ror:updatePeriod>weekly</ror:updatePeriod>
     <ror:sortOrder>1</ror:sortOrder>
     <ror:resourceOf>sitemap</ror:resourceOf>
</item>
<item>
     <link>http://www.edoxitraining.com/primavera-p6-training-course-in-dubai</link>
     <title>Primavera Training - Certified Primavera P6 Courses in Dubai  </title>
     <description>Advance Primavera P6 Course is the perfect course for project management! Our Primavera training courses helpful for project managers, program managers and project planners to execute and monitor their projects easily. Call us for further inquiry! </description>
     <ror:updatePeriod>weekly</ror:updatePeriod>
     <ror:sortOrder>1</ror:sortOrder>
     <ror:resourceOf>sitemap</ror:resourceOf>
</item>
<item>
     <link>http://www.edoxitraining.com/category/microsoft-courses-in-dubai</link>
     <title>Microsoft Office Training Courses in Dubai, UAE | Edoxi Training Institute</title>
     <description>Improve your Microsoft Office Knowledge &amp; Skills with our expert trainers in Dubai! We designed MS courses for individuals who are working in small, medium or large organization. Learn easily maintain sheets, create slides for presentations &amp; other advanc</description>
     <ror:updatePeriod>weekly</ror:updatePeriod>
     <ror:sortOrder>1</ror:sortOrder>
     <ror:resourceOf>sitemap</ror:resourceOf>
</item>
<item>
     <link>http://www.edoxitraining.com/advanced-access-training-course-in-dubai</link>
     <title>Advanced Microsoft Access Training Institute in Dubai | Edoxi Training Institute  </title>
     <description>MS Access Training Courses - Leading Institute of providing advanced Microsoft Access Training Courses for you to expand your current expertise, knowledge on creating and altering table structures, relational database creation, working with reports, forms</description>
     <ror:updatePeriod>weekly</ror:updatePeriod>
     <ror:sortOrder>1</ror:sortOrder>
     <ror:resourceOf>sitemap</ror:resourceOf>
</item>
<item>
     <link>http://www.edoxitraining.com/advanced-excel-training-course-in-dubai</link>
     <title>Advanced Excel Courses in Dubai, UAE | Edoxi Training Institute  </title>
     <description>Advanced Excel Training courses driven exceptionally experienced Microsoft Excel coaches to learn advanced functions, formulas, data handling process and utilizing advanced features on worksheet, work with controls and record macros. Call us and Start Tod</description>
     <ror:updatePeriod>weekly</ror:updatePeriod>
     <ror:sortOrder>1</ror:sortOrder>
     <ror:resourceOf>sitemap</ror:resourceOf>
</item>
<item>
     <link>http://www.edoxitraining.com/advanced-ms-office-training-course-in-dubai</link>
     <title>Advance Microsoft Office Training in Dubai | Edoxi Training Institute  </title>
     <description>Join our advanced Microsoft Office Training to enhance your work productivity! We designed Microsoft training courses for professionals who want to learn most significant time-saving tools and shortcuts related to PowerPoint, Word, Outlook and Excel to en</description>
     <ror:updatePeriod>weekly</ror:updatePeriod>
     <ror:sortOrder>1</ror:sortOrder>
     <ror:resourceOf>sitemap</ror:resourceOf>
</item>
<item>
     <link>http://www.edoxitraining.com/ms-access-training-course-in-dubai</link>
     <title>Microsoft Access Training in Dubai, MS Access Certification Courses | Edoxi Training Institute  </title>
     <description>Attend MS Access training courses in Dubai driven by highly experienced MS Access mentors with numerous experiences for each with quite unique approach. MS Access is utilized mostly in business for information administration &amp; capacity. Used to track and </description>
     <ror:updatePeriod>weekly</ror:updatePeriod>
     <ror:sortOrder>1</ror:sortOrder>
     <ror:resourceOf>sitemap</ror:resourceOf>
</item>
<item>
     <link>http://www.edoxitraining.com/ms-excel-training-course-in-dubai</link>
     <title>Excel Courses in Dubai - Microsoft Excel Training Courses in Dubai, UAE  </title>
     <description>Grab wonderful opportunity to learn advance feature of MS Excel at Edoxi Training Center! MS Excel training makes easy to screen monetary execution, business benefit, figure instalments on vast buys, design a financial plan, or remain composed with agenda</description>
     <ror:updatePeriod>weekly</ror:updatePeriod>
     <ror:sortOrder>1</ror:sortOrder>
     <ror:resourceOf>sitemap</ror:resourceOf>
</item>
<item>
     <link>http://www.edoxitraining.com/ms-office-training-course-in-dubai</link>
     <title>MS Office Training - Best MS Office Classes in Dubai | Edoxi Training Institute  </title>
     <description>MS Office Training in Dubai - Knowledge of Microsoft Tools is mandatory in today’s job market. Join our Microsoft office course from renowned training institutes in Dubai and Get Microsoft office certification to work anywhere. Reach us now at +971 438016</description>
     <ror:updatePeriod>weekly</ror:updatePeriod>
     <ror:sortOrder>1</ror:sortOrder>
     <ror:resourceOf>sitemap</ror:resourceOf>
</item>
<item>
     <link>http://www.edoxitraining.com/ms-outlook-training-course-in-dubai</link>
     <title>MS Outlook Training Courses in Dubai, UAE | Edoxi Training Institute  </title>
     <description>Promote your career through MS Outlook Training courses from Edoxi Training Center! Specially designed outlook courses to figure out how to utilize MS Outlook to its maximum capacity to manage your own emails, tasks etc. efficiently!  </description>
     <ror:updatePeriod>weekly</ror:updatePeriod>
     <ror:sortOrder>1</ror:sortOrder>
     <ror:resourceOf>sitemap</ror:resourceOf>
</item>
<item>
     <link>http://www.edoxitraining.com/ms-powerpoint-training-course-in-dubai</link>
     <title>MS PowerPoint Training Courses in Dubai | Edoxi Training Institute  </title>
     <description>Become MS PowerPoint specialist in Dubai with Edoxi Training Institute! Microsoft PowerPoint enables you to make charming slide introductions that can be effortlessly be shared on the web. Our training will enable you to figure out how to utilize Microsof</description>
     <ror:updatePeriod>weekly</ror:updatePeriod>
     <ror:sortOrder>1</ror:sortOrder>
     <ror:resourceOf>sitemap</ror:resourceOf>
</item>
<item>
     <link>http://www.edoxitraining.com/ms-word-training-course-in-dubai</link>
     <title>Microsoft Word Training in Dubai - MS Word Course Certification | Edoxi Training Institute  </title>
     <description>Looking for MS Word training institute in Dubai? Join our MS Word training course to get advanced tips &amp; tricks to improve MS Word processing skills effectively at each phase. Best MS Office certification institute, call at +971 43801666.</description>
     <ror:updatePeriod>weekly</ror:updatePeriod>
     <ror:sortOrder>1</ror:sortOrder>
     <ror:resourceOf>sitemap</ror:resourceOf>
</item>
<item>
     <link>http://www.edoxitraining.com/category/test-preparation-courses-in-dubai</link>
     <title>Test Preparation Courses - IELTS, PTE Training Classes in Dubai </title>
     <description>Test preparation courses are the perfect way to crack the IELTS, OET, PTE and other similar exams easily! Our training courses are carefully designed and structured to provide the quality training to individuals for cracking the exams. </description>
     <ror:updatePeriod>weekly</ror:updatePeriod>
     <ror:sortOrder>1</ror:sortOrder>
     <ror:resourceOf>sitemap</ror:resourceOf>
</item>
<item>
     <link>http://www.edoxitraining.com/ielts-training-course-in-dubai</link>
     <title>IELTS Preparation Courses - IELTS Training Center in Dubai  </title>
     <description>IELTS Courses in Dubai - Trusted IELTS Coaching Centre offering IELTS preparation courses for students to strength your skills in English, listening, reading, writing and speaking. Our experts will train you effectively at every point to pass IELTS Test e</description>
     <ror:updatePeriod>weekly</ror:updatePeriod>
     <ror:sortOrder>1</ror:sortOrder>
     <ror:resourceOf>sitemap</ror:resourceOf>
</item>
<item>
     <link>http://www.edoxitraining.com/medical-coding-training-course-in-dubai</link>
     <title>Medical Coding Courses in Dubai | Edoxi Training Institute  </title>
     <description>Looking for career opportunity in medical field? Fantastic opportunity to join Medical Coding Courses at Edoxi Training Institute! Our Courses help individuals to understand &amp; learn healthcare diagnosis, procedures, medical services and equipment into uni</description>
     <ror:updatePeriod>weekly</ror:updatePeriod>
     <ror:sortOrder>1</ror:sortOrder>
     <ror:resourceOf>sitemap</ror:resourceOf>
</item>
<item>
     <link>http://www.edoxitraining.com/oet-training-course-in-dubai</link>
     <title>OET Preparation Training Course in Dubai | Edoxi Training Institute  </title>
     <description>OET test is recognized English language test the healthcare professionals. Get professional OET training from extremely qualified experts in English language and you are sure to succeed OET test.</description>
     <ror:updatePeriod>weekly</ror:updatePeriod>
     <ror:sortOrder>1</ror:sortOrder>
     <ror:resourceOf>sitemap</ror:resourceOf>
</item>
<item>
     <link>http://www.edoxitraining.com/pte-training-course-in-dubai</link>
     <title>PTE Preparation Classes in Dubai | Edoxi Training Institute  </title>
     <description>Start PTE Preparation course for a dream career with Edoxi Training Institute Dubai! Our PTE preparation classes help our students who are much interested for higher study in abroad or move to an English-speaking country like USA, UK, Australia, New Zeala</description>
     <ror:updatePeriod>weekly</ror:updatePeriod>
     <ror:sortOrder>1</ror:sortOrder>
     <ror:resourceOf>sitemap</ror:resourceOf>
</item>
<item>
     <link>http://www.edoxitraining.com/toefl-training-course-in-dubai</link>
     <title>TOEFL Preparation Program in Dubai - Edoxi Training Institute  </title>
     <description>Our quality TOEFL preparation training courses will help you to crack this exam by increasing your test score in reading, listening, speaking &amp; writing English efficiently in Dubai. Choose our institute for TOEFL training to know your English proficiency!</description>
     <ror:updatePeriod>weekly</ror:updatePeriod>
     <ror:sortOrder>1</ror:sortOrder>
     <ror:resourceOf>sitemap</ror:resourceOf>
</item>
<item>
     <link>http://www.edoxitraining.com/category/programming-courses-in-dubai</link>
     <title>Advanced Programming Courses in Dubai | Edoxi Training Institute</title>
     <description>Learn advanced programming to bring your career to the next level!  Our programming courses includes .Net, ASP.NET, C++, C Programming, JAVA, MS SQL, Visual Basic etc. We have modern computer labs that will always help you to work and get trained effectiv</description>
     <ror:updatePeriod>weekly</ror:updatePeriod>
     <ror:sortOrder>1</ror:sortOrder>
     <ror:resourceOf>sitemap</ror:resourceOf>
</item>
<item>
     <link>http://www.edoxitraining.com/.net-training-course-in-dubai</link>
     <title>.Net Training - ASP.NET Training Course in Abu Dhabi, Dubai   </title>
     <description>Improve your programming skills on ASP.Net Platform! Edoxi Training Institute offers various asp.net programming courses for beginners, and .net professionals to enhance their knowledge to develop any application easily. Enquire now to book your seat! </description>
     <ror:updatePeriod>weekly</ror:updatePeriod>
     <ror:sortOrder>1</ror:sortOrder>
     <ror:resourceOf>sitemap</ror:resourceOf>
</item>
<item>
     <link>http://www.edoxitraining.com/asp-.net-training-course-in-dubai</link>
     <title>ASP.NET Training in Dubai - Top Rated ASP.NET Programming Training Institute  </title>
     <description>Get ASP.NET training from recognized training institute of Dubai! Qualified professionals will be with the students at their every step in learning ASP.NET course. Less number of students in each batch to understand sessions effectively! Join our ASP.NET </description>
     <ror:updatePeriod>weekly</ror:updatePeriod>
     <ror:sortOrder>1</ror:sortOrder>
     <ror:resourceOf>sitemap</ror:resourceOf>
</item>
<item>
     <link>http://www.edoxitraining.com/c-plus-plus-programming-course-in-dubai</link>
     <title>C++ Training in Dubai - C++ Programming Language Courses | Edoxi Training Institute  </title>
     <description>Get advanced training of object-oriented programming language C++ at Edoxi Training Center in Dubai! Our programing courses and comprehensive study material help you to understand the basic concepts, structures, advanced virtual functions and templates to</description>
     <ror:updatePeriod>weekly</ror:updatePeriod>
     <ror:sortOrder>1</ror:sortOrder>
     <ror:resourceOf>sitemap</ror:resourceOf>
</item>
<item>
     <link>http://www.edoxitraining.com/c-programming-training-course-in-dubai</link>
     <title>C Programming Language Courses in Dubai - Edoxi Training Institute  </title>
     <description>C Programming training at Edoxi will enhance basic programming skills in the students which help in solving the higher level and difficult programming logics. We covers main function arguments, work on structures, arrays, build variables, generating point</description>
     <ror:updatePeriod>weekly</ror:updatePeriod>
     <ror:sortOrder>1</ror:sortOrder>
     <ror:resourceOf>sitemap</ror:resourceOf>
</item>
<item>
     <link>http://www.edoxitraining.com/excel-vba-training-course-in-dubai</link>
     <title>Microsoft Excel VBA Training in Dubai - Edoxi Training Institute  </title>
     <description>Extend your skills of recorded macros utilizing Excel VBA with our finest and advance Excel training in Dubai by our professional experts! One stop solution for Excel VBA courses needs for individuals who are beginners in Excel programming. Give us a call</description>
     <ror:updatePeriod>weekly</ror:updatePeriod>
     <ror:sortOrder>1</ror:sortOrder>
     <ror:resourceOf>sitemap</ror:resourceOf>
</item>
<item>
     <link>http://www.edoxitraining.com/java-training-course-in-dubai</link>
     <title>Java Training - Java Developer Training Program in Dubai  </title>
     <description>Develop Your Java programming skills through advance Java training program at Edoxi Traning! Our special designed Java programming courses perfect for professionals to get good knowledge of core Java, JDBC Architecture, J-unit frame work. Become an expert</description>
     <ror:updatePeriod>weekly</ror:updatePeriod>
     <ror:sortOrder>1</ror:sortOrder>
     <ror:resourceOf>sitemap</ror:resourceOf>
</item>
<item>
     <link>http://www.edoxitraining.com/ms-sql-server-training-course-in-dubai</link>
     <title>SQL Server Courses - MS SQL Certified Training Program in Dubai  </title>
     <description>Edoxi Training Institute provide MS SQL server training courses in Dubai by professional instructors to understand the concept of SQL Server programming language, joins, queries, sub queries, relational databases, unions etc. Become an expert in SQL Serve</description>
     <ror:updatePeriod>weekly</ror:updatePeriod>
     <ror:sortOrder>1</ror:sortOrder>
     <ror:resourceOf>sitemap</ror:resourceOf>
</item>
<item>
     <link>http://www.edoxitraining.com/visual-basic-training-course-in-dubai</link>
     <title>Visual Basic Training Courses for Beginners in Dubai | Edoxi Training Institute  </title>
     <description>Join job-oriented Visual Basic Training Courses at Edoxi Training Center! Practical visual basic program training gives you a complete intro to the use of Visual Basic and improves your skills enough to write a programming code effectively. Call us for re</description>
     <ror:updatePeriod>weekly</ror:updatePeriod>
     <ror:sortOrder>1</ror:sortOrder>
     <ror:resourceOf>sitemap</ror:resourceOf>
</item>
<item>
     <link>http://www.edoxitraining.com/category/language-courses-in-dubai</link>
     <title>Language Courses in Dubai - Enhance Business Writing Skills </title>
     <description>Language courses are important for individuals to enhance your business writing skills. Our English grammar, spoken English, advanced English courses will give you the right kind of basics to speak fluently and communicate better with everyone.</description>
     <ror:updatePeriod>weekly</ror:updatePeriod>
     <ror:sortOrder>1</ror:sortOrder>
     <ror:resourceOf>sitemap</ror:resourceOf>
</item>
<item>
     <link>http://www.edoxitraining.com/advanced-english-training-course-in-dubai</link>
     <title>English Language Courses Dubai - Advanced English Training | Edoxi Training Institute  </title>
     <description>Join Advanced English Language Courses in Dubai to boost your speaking skills and take yourself to the next level. Our experienced teacher provides complete training to improve your English writing and speaking skills with friends and colleagues easily. E</description>
     <ror:updatePeriod>weekly</ror:updatePeriod>
     <ror:sortOrder>1</ror:sortOrder>
     <ror:resourceOf>sitemap</ror:resourceOf>
</item>
<item>
     <link>http://www.edoxitraining.com/email-writing-course-in-dubai</link>
     <title>Professional Email Writing Training in Dubai - Edoxi Training Institute  </title>
     <description>Email Writing training course is extremely demanding course in Dubai! We provide professional email writing training for individuals as well as corporates. Our trainers have tons of experience in providing right training on how to write a professional ema</description>
     <ror:updatePeriod>weekly</ror:updatePeriod>
     <ror:sortOrder>1</ror:sortOrder>
     <ror:resourceOf>sitemap</ror:resourceOf>
</item>
<item>
     <link>http://www.edoxitraining.com/spoken-arabic-training-course-in-dubai</link>
     <title>Arabic Speaking Classes - Arabic Language Courses in Dubai  </title>
     <description>Want to learn Arabic Language? Join our Special Arabic Speaking Classes in Dubai. Our Arabic Language Courses provide intense Arabic training, speaking and listening practice, introduction to alphabets and vocabulary, exercises, listening to audio dialogu</description>
     <ror:updatePeriod>weekly</ror:updatePeriod>
     <ror:sortOrder>1</ror:sortOrder>
     <ror:resourceOf>sitemap</ror:resourceOf>
</item>
<item>
     <link>http://www.edoxitraining.com/business-writing-skills-training-course-in-dubai</link>
     <title>English Writing Courses Dubai - Business Writing Skills | Edoxi Training Institute  </title>
     <description>Grab opportunities to learn English Writing skills at Edoxi Training Institute!  Develop your English writing standard to write emails such as business documents, emails to clients, reports or any agenda. You will easily make your work life very productiv</description>
     <ror:updatePeriod>weekly</ror:updatePeriod>
     <ror:sortOrder>1</ror:sortOrder>
     <ror:resourceOf>sitemap</ror:resourceOf>
</item>
<item>
     <link>http://www.edoxitraining.com/spoken-english-training-course-in-dubai</link>
     <title>English Speaking Courses - Spoken English Classes in Dubai  </title>
     <description>Join our spoken English classes to improve your English speaking skills in just a few weeks! Our English speaking courses help the students to learn advance techniques to speak English with flow. The art of public speaking, group discussions and two-way s</description>
     <ror:updatePeriod>weekly</ror:updatePeriod>
     <ror:sortOrder>1</ror:sortOrder>
     <ror:resourceOf>sitemap</ror:resourceOf>
</item>
<item>
     <link>http://www.edoxitraining.com/category/accounting-courses-in-dubai</link>
     <title>Accounting Courses - Accounting Training Classes in Dubai </title>
     <description>Join Accoutring Certificate courses at Edoxi training institute Dubai for bright future! Our Advance accounting courses such as Tally, Peachtree, Sage 50, QuickBooks, and other courses help you to become master in accounting, finance, audit, law financial</description>
     <ror:updatePeriod>weekly</ror:updatePeriod>
     <ror:sortOrder>1</ror:sortOrder>
     <ror:resourceOf>sitemap</ror:resourceOf>
</item>
<item>
     <link>http://www.edoxitraining.com/accounting-for-non-accountants-training-course-in-dubai</link>
     <title>Accounting Short Courses in Dubai - Accounting for Non-Accountants Training Courses   </title>
     <description>Get yourself trained on basics of accounting and analysis of financial statement with our short accounting courses in Dubai. Our accounting for non-accountants courses specially designed by real-life case studies which help individuals in their career gro</description>
     <ror:updatePeriod>weekly</ror:updatePeriod>
     <ror:sortOrder>1</ror:sortOrder>
     <ror:resourceOf>sitemap</ror:resourceOf>
</item>
<item>
     <link>http://www.edoxitraining.com/financial-accounting-training-course-in-dubai</link>
     <title>Financial Accounting Courses in Dubai | Edoxi Training Institute  </title>
     <description>Recognized financial training institute provides advanced financial training for interested candidates to understand the accounting concepts such as accounting equation, recording transactions, prepare and analyse financial statements etc.</description>
     <ror:updatePeriod>weekly</ror:updatePeriod>
     <ror:sortOrder>1</ror:sortOrder>
     <ror:resourceOf>sitemap</ror:resourceOf>
</item>
<item>
     <link>http://www.edoxitraining.com/peachtree-training-course-in-dubai</link>
     <title>Peachtree Training Courses in Dubai | Edoxi Training Institute  </title>
     <description>Get benefits for advance Peachtree Training courses to automate and handle various accounting tasks such as integration of accounts to be paid, received, creating statements of finance, check invoices, etc. Join Peachtree with VAT training courses at Edox</description>
     <ror:updatePeriod>weekly</ror:updatePeriod>
     <ror:sortOrder>1</ror:sortOrder>
     <ror:resourceOf>sitemap</ror:resourceOf>
</item>
<item>
     <link>http://www.edoxitraining.com/quickbooks-training-course-in-dubai</link>
     <title>Quick Books Training Courses in Dubai | Edoxi Training Institute  </title>
     <description>QuickBooks is accounting software used by small and medium scale businesses to manage business payments, administer and disburse bills etc. We provide advanced training of accounting software Quick Books to improve your business at affordable prices.  </description>
     <ror:updatePeriod>weekly</ror:updatePeriod>
     <ror:sortOrder>1</ror:sortOrder>
     <ror:resourceOf>sitemap</ror:resourceOf>
</item>
<item>
     <link>http://www.edoxitraining.com/tally-training-course-in-dubai</link>
     <title>Tally Courses - Tally Training Institutes in Dubai  </title>
     <description>Learn Tally training to get advantage in accounting and the financial world! Our expert have designed Tally course in such way for anyone to understand it and easily use with Vat, inventory &amp; other features of the Tally software. Call us and Join Now!</description>
     <ror:updatePeriod>weekly</ror:updatePeriod>
     <ror:sortOrder>1</ror:sortOrder>
     <ror:resourceOf>sitemap</ror:resourceOf>
</item>
<item>
     <link>http://www.edoxitraining.com/zoho-books-training-course-in-dubai</link>
     <title>Zoho Books Accounting Training in Dubai | Edoxi Training Institute  </title>
     <description>Zoho Books is the most used accounting software in the organizations that makes it easy daily management of finances for a small scale business. Our Zoho Books program offers bookkeepers &amp; accountants the tools to turn into Zoho books expert in Dubai.</description>
     <ror:updatePeriod>weekly</ror:updatePeriod>
     <ror:sortOrder>1</ror:sortOrder>
     <ror:resourceOf>sitemap</ror:resourceOf>
</item>
<item>
     <link>http://www.edoxitraining.com/vat-training-course-in-dubai</link>
     <title>Vat Training in Dubai - Value Added Tax (VAT) Training Courses  </title>
     <description>Value Added Tax (VAT) utilised on goods and services imposed at every sale point. Edoxi training institute offering VAT Training Courses at reasonable prices. Our unique ways of learning and teaching methodologies helps our students to learn and understan</description>
     <ror:updatePeriod>weekly</ror:updatePeriod>
     <ror:sortOrder>1</ror:sortOrder>
     <ror:resourceOf>sitemap</ror:resourceOf>
</item>
<item>
     <link>http://www.edoxitraining.com/category/management-courses-in-dubai</link>
     <title>Affordable Management Training Courses in Dubai | Edoxi Training Institute</title>
     <description>Establish yourself in organization with our quality and worthy Management Training in Dubai! Join our management courses which include business management skills, HR Management, Presentation Skill, Procurement Management and warehouse management to suppor</description>
     <ror:updatePeriod>weekly</ror:updatePeriod>
     <ror:sortOrder>1</ror:sortOrder>
     <ror:resourceOf>sitemap</ror:resourceOf>
</item>
<item>
     <link>http://www.edoxitraining.com/business-management-training-course-in-dubai</link>
     <title>Business Management Courses in Abu Dhabi, Dubai, UAE| Edoxi Training Institute  </title>
     <description>Improve Your Business Management Skills easily at Edoxi Training Institute! We offer short term and long term business management courses for professionals to take their business on next level without any stress and difficulties. Call for more inquiries</description>
     <ror:updatePeriod>weekly</ror:updatePeriod>
     <ror:sortOrder>1</ror:sortOrder>
     <ror:resourceOf>sitemap</ror:resourceOf>
</item>
<item>
     <link>http://www.edoxitraining.com/hr-management-training-course-in-dubai</link>
     <title>HR Training Courses in Dubai - HR Management Professionals (CHRP) Courses  </title>
     <description>HR Training Course Dubai - CHRP is most amazing certification for human resource professionals to learn advanced techniques to manage many things such as payroll &amp; leaves management, timings, scheduling meetings etc. in the organization. Join Course at To</description>
     <ror:updatePeriod>weekly</ror:updatePeriod>
     <ror:sortOrder>1</ror:sortOrder>
     <ror:resourceOf>sitemap</ror:resourceOf>
</item>
<item>
     <link>http://www.edoxitraining.com/presentation-skills-training-course-in-dubai</link>
     <title>Presentation Skills Training Courses in Dubai | Edoxi Training Institute  </title>
     <description>Delivering effective presentations to a large audience is essential to convince colleagues, clients or energizing team! Our presentation skill training courses help professionals to improve their presentation designs to give outstanding presentation in an</description>
     <ror:updatePeriod>weekly</ror:updatePeriod>
     <ror:sortOrder>1</ror:sortOrder>
     <ror:resourceOf>sitemap</ror:resourceOf>
</item>
<item>
     <link>http://www.edoxitraining.com/purchase-management-training-course-in-dubai</link>
     <title>Certified Purchasing Professional Courses (CPP) in Dubai | Edoxi Training Institute  </title>
     <description>Polish your professional purchasing skills through our certified purchase training courses in Dubai! CPP Courses helps professionals to understand procurement cost, recognise the business strength, utilise projects at lower cost, better practice on contra</description>
     <ror:updatePeriod>weekly</ror:updatePeriod>
     <ror:sortOrder>1</ror:sortOrder>
     <ror:resourceOf>sitemap</ror:resourceOf>
</item>
<item>
     <link>http://www.edoxitraining.com/supply-chain-and-logistics-training-course-in-dubai</link>
     <title>Logistics Courses - Supply Chain Management Courses in Dubai  </title>
     <description>Boost your Career with Logistics and Supply Chain management courses in Dubai! Professional Training Center “Edoxi Training” offers opportunities to become certified Supply Chain and Logistics professional to make use of management concepts for proficient</description>
     <ror:updatePeriod>weekly</ror:updatePeriod>
     <ror:sortOrder>1</ror:sortOrder>
     <ror:resourceOf>sitemap</ror:resourceOf>
</item>
<item>
     <link>http://www.edoxitraining.com/warehouse-management-training-course-in-dubai</link>
     <title>Warehouse Management Training - Dubai Warehouse Management Certification   </title>
     <description>Warehouse management training is crucial to get clear understanding of estimating the flow of material &amp; workloads in warehouses effectively. Improve skills for maintenance &amp; safety inside the warehouse with our warehouse management training in Dubai!</description>
     <ror:updatePeriod>weekly</ror:updatePeriod>
     <ror:sortOrder>1</ror:sortOrder>
     <ror:resourceOf>sitemap</ror:resourceOf>
</item>
<item>
     <link>http://www.edoxitraining.com/courses</link>
     <title>Courses - Edoxi Training Center - Dubai, UAE</title>
     <description>Courses - Edoxi Training Center - Dubai, UAE</description>
     <ror:updatePeriod>weekly</ror:updatePeriod>
     <ror:sortOrder>1</ror:sortOrder>
     <ror:resourceOf>sitemap</ror:resourceOf>
</item>
<item>
     <link>http://www.edoxitraining.com/corporate-training</link>
     <title>Corporate Training Companies in Dubai, UAE | Edoxi Training Institute</title>
     <description>Fastest Growing Corporate Training institute provides corporate training program to develop your employee key skills which leads to improvement in the overall productivity of the business.  Reach us today!</description>
     <ror:updatePeriod>weekly</ror:updatePeriod>
     <ror:sortOrder>1</ror:sortOrder>
     <ror:resourceOf>sitemap</ror:resourceOf>
</item>
<item>
     <link>http://www.edoxitraining.com/accreditations</link>
     <title>Accreditations - Edoxi Training Center - Dubai, UAE</title>
     <description>Accreditations - Edoxi Training Center - Dubai, UAE</description>
     <ror:updatePeriod>weekly</ror:updatePeriod>
     <ror:sortOrder>1</ror:sortOrder>
     <ror:resourceOf>sitemap</ror:resourceOf>
</item>
<item>
     <link>http://www.edoxitraining.com/testimonial</link>
     <title>Student Testimonial - Edoxi Training Center - Dubai, UAE</title>
     <description>Student Testimonial - Edoxi Training Center - Dubai, UAE</description>
     <ror:updatePeriod>weekly</ror:updatePeriod>
     <ror:sortOrder>1</ror:sortOrder>
     <ror:resourceOf>sitemap</ror:resourceOf>
</item>
<item>
     <link>http://www.edoxitraining.com/blog</link>
     <title>Blog - Edoxi Training Center - Dubai, UAE</title>
     <description>Blog - Edoxi Training Center - Dubai, UAE</description>
     <ror:updatePeriod>weekly</ror:updatePeriod>
     <ror:sortOrder>1</ror:sortOrder>
     <ror:resourceOf>sitemap</ror:resourceOf>
</item>
<item>
     <link>http://www.edoxitraining.com/faqs</link>
     <title>FAQs - Edoxi Training Center - Dubai, UAE</title>
     <description>FAQs - Edoxi Training Center - Dubai, UAE</description>
     <ror:updatePeriod>weekly</ror:updatePeriod>
     <ror:sortOrder>1</ror:sortOrder>
     <ror:resourceOf>sitemap</ror:resourceOf>
</item>
<item>
     <link>http://www.edoxitraining.com/contact</link>
     <title>Contact Us - Edoxi Training Center - Dubai, UAE</title>
     <description>Contact Us - Edoxi Training Center - Dubai, UAE</description>
     <ror:updatePeriod>weekly</ror:updatePeriod>
     <ror:sortOrder>1</ror:sortOrder>
     <ror:resourceOf>sitemap</ror:resourceOf>
</item>
<item>
     <link>http://www.edoxitraining.com/gallery</link>
     <title>Gallery - Edoxi Training Center - Dubai, UAE</title>
     <description>Gallery - Edoxi Training Center - Dubai, UAE</description>
     <ror:updatePeriod>weekly</ror:updatePeriod>
     <ror:sortOrder>1</ror:sortOrder>
     <ror:resourceOf>sitemap</ror:resourceOf>
</item>
<item>
     <link>http://www.edoxitraining.com/sitemap</link>
     <title>Sitemap - Edoxi Training Center - Dubai, UAE</title>
     <description>Sitemap - Edoxi Training Center - Dubai, UAE</description>
     <ror:updatePeriod>weekly</ror:updatePeriod>
     <ror:sortOrder>1</ror:sortOrder>
     <ror:resourceOf>sitemap</ror:resourceOf>
</item>
<item>
     <link>http://www.edoxitraining.com/privacy-policy</link>
     <title>Privacy Policy - Edoxi Training Center - Dubai, UAE</title>
     <description>Privacy Policy - Edoxi Training Center - Dubai, UAE</description>
     <ror:updatePeriod>weekly</ror:updatePeriod>
     <ror:sortOrder>1</ror:sortOrder>
     <ror:resourceOf>sitemap</ror:resourceOf>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>
  